

Jeff Berlin

in linkedin.com/in/jeff-berlin • github.com/jeffberlin

Web Developer

☑ jeff@jbrally.com 📞 (302) 463-5129 👂 Wilmington, NC

About Me

Motivated web developer with 2+ years of experience in designing and creating custom websites using multiple languages, frameworks, and tools. Strong communication skills, team player, pays close attention to detail, enjoys problem solving, and has a desire to learn.

Skills

Development: HTML / HTML5, CSS, Bootstrap, Foundation, Javascript, JQuery, AngularJS, React, React-Native, Redux, KnockoutJS, WordPress, PHP, JSON, AJAX, Python, SQL, Postgres, C++, Open Graph, Responsive Web Design, Jasmine Unit Testing, Heroku

Design: Adobe Photoshop, Adobe InDesign, Adobe XD, Adobe Illustrator, Sketch

Other: Slack, Microsoft Office, Automotive, Logistics, Analytics

Experience

BMT Micro, Inc. - Web Developer

April 2018 - Present | Wilmington, NC

- Redesigned and built the new product catalog, blog, customer and vendor help pages, and email response template.
- Created a WordPress Plugin that integrates with BMT's shopping cart and vendor product information.
- Assist with any technical issues and questions.

TRU Colors Brewing - UI/UX Developer (Contractor)

December 2017 - April 2018 | Wilmington, NC

- Designed, built, and maintained the company website.
- Designed and created brochures and flyers for their advertising campaigns.

JOMO, Inc. - Front End Web Developer

January 2017 - December 2017 | Wilmington, NC

- Built and maintained the company website based on the wireframes.
- Assisted with graphic design duties for webpages and advertising.
- Worked closely with the CEO and Marketing team to design and create content for advertising and prize giveaways.
- Consulted with mobile development team on app features and proper design wireframes.

Education

Udacity - C++ Nanodegree

March 2019 - Present

Udacity - React/React-Native/Redux Nanodegree

June 2018 - October 2018

Udacity - Front End Web Development Nanodegree

August 2016 - March 2017